this problem asks us to
reformat the case statement that we've
been given
so that it only takes up five lines
again we can take advantage of ruby's
expressiveness here
to place each condition of our case
statement
and its operation on a single line
we can do this using the reserved word
then
so i'll move these onto one line
now we don't need to use then with else
because we don't provide
any specific condition to else our code
right now
looks a little bit messy so let's clean
it up by formatting our code properly
we want to properly align the operation
associated with each condition
so that our code remains clear and
readable
previously our case statement took up
eight lines
reformatting our case statement using
the reserved word then
led to our code being only five lines
and yet the code is still very readable
this code retains the same functionality
that our
original case statement provided
reformatting our case statement this way
works well because we only have one
operation
in each clause of our case statement
which is
invoking put us and outputting a string
if we needed to perform multiple
operations within the clauses of our
when statement
such as calculate a value and then
output it
then we wouldn't want to use the shorter
syntax
it wouldn't be readable we would want to
put each operation in our clauses
on its own line however in a case like
this
where we only perform one action in each
clause
it works well
you